const questionsData = [
    {
        question: "What word is being said in this clip?",
        media: '',
        answers: ["日本 - にほん - Japan", "二本 - にほん - Two (of something long and cylidrical)"],
        correctAnswer: "二本 - にほん - Two (of something long and cylindrical)",
        questionNumber: 1
    },

    {
        question: "What word is being said in this clip?",
        media: '',
        answers: ["本当 - ほんとう - Really, truth", "本島 - ほんとう -  Main island"],
        correctAnswer: "本島 - ほんとう -  Main island",
        questionNumber: 2
    },

    {
        question: "What word is being said in this clip?",
        media: '',
        answers: ["石 - いし - Stone", "医師 - いし - Doctor"],
        correctAnswer: "石 - いし - Stone",
        questionNumber: 3 
    },

    {
        question: "What word is being said in this clip?",
        media: '',
        answers: ["一 - いち - One", "位置 - いち - Position, location"],
        correctAnswer: "位置 - いち - Position, location",
        questionNumber: 4 
    },

    {
        question: "What word is being said in this clip?",
        media: '',
        answers: ["年 - とし - Year, age", "都市 - とし - City"],
        correctAnswer: "年 - とし - Year, age",
        questionNumber: 5
    },

    {
        question: "What word is being said in this clip?",
        media: '',
        answers: ["春 - はる - Spring", "貼る - はる - To stick"],
        correctAnswer: "春 - はる - Spring",
        questionNumber: 6
    },

    {
        question: "What word is being said in this clip?",
        media: '',
        answers: ["白 - しろ - White", "城 - しろ -  Castle"],
        correctAnswer: "白 - しろ - White",
        questionNumber: 7
    },

    {
        question: "What word is being said in this clip?",
        media: '',
        answers: ["雨 - あめ - Rain", "飴 - あめ - Hard candy"],
        correctAnswer: "飴 - あめ - Hard candy",
        questionNumber: 8
    },

    {
        question: "What word is being said in this clip?",
        media: '',
        answers: ["道 - みち - Road, path", "未知 - みち - Unknown"],
        correctAnswer: "道 - みち - Road, path",
        questionNumber: 9
    },

    {
        question: "What word is being said in this clip?",
        media: '',
        answers: ["機能が - きのう - Function", "昨日が - きのう - Yesterday]"],
        correctAnswer: "昨日が - きのう - Yesterday",
        questionNumber: 10
    }
]

export default questionsData